Mexicans, at the cry of war,
make ready the steel and the bridle,
and may the Earth tremble at its core
at the resounding roar of the cannon.
at the resounding roar of the cannon!
Gird, Oh Fatherland!, your temples with olive
by the peace of the divine archangel,
for in heaven your eternal destiny
was written by the finger of God.
If, however, a foreign enemy would dare
to profane your ground with its sole,
think "Oh beloved Fatherland!" that Heaven
has given you a soldier in every son.
A soldier in every son!
Mexicans, at the cry of war,
make ready the steel and the bridle,
and may the Earth tremble at its core
at the resounding roar of the cannon.
at the resounding roar of the cannon!